export const data = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How would you describe your mood stability on a typical day?",
      "options": [
        "Stable",
        "Occasionally fluctuating",
        "Frequently fluctuating",
        "Extreme mood swings"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Stable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you experience episodes of elevated mood or energy followed by depressive periods?",
      "options": [
        "No, not at all",
        "Occasionally",
        "Frequently",
        "Yes, regularly"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No, not at all"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you ever been told by others that your behavior during certain periods seems unusual or extreme?",
      "options": [
        "Never",
        "Rarely",
        "Sometimes",
        "Frequently"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Never"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does your ability to concentrate and make decisions change during mood episodes?",
      "options": [
        "No significant change",
        "Slight impairment",
        "Moderate impairment",
        "Severe impairment"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No significant change"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you engage in impulsive or risky behaviors during elevated mood periods?",
      "options": [
        "Never",
        "Rarely",
        "Sometimes",
        "Frequently"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Never"
    },
    {
      "question": "How long do your mood episodes typically last?",
      "options": [
        "A few hours",
        "Several days",
        "Weeks",
        "Months"
      ],
      "correctOption": "A few hours"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you sought professional help or been diagnosed with a mood disorder, such as bipolar disorder?",
      "options": [
        "Yes",
        "Considering it",
        "No, not yet",
        "No, and I don't plan to"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Considering it"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you experienced significant disruptions in your personal or professional life due to mood swings?",
      "options": [
        "No disruptions",
        "Slight disruptions",
        "Moderate disruptions",
        "Severe disruptions"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No disruptions"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you have a family history of mood disorders, including bipolar disorder?",
      "options": [
        "No family history",
        "Uncertain",
        "Yes, some family history",
        "Yes, significant family history"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No family history"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you believe that addressing and managing mood stability is important for overall well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Strongly agree",
        "Agree",
        "Neutral",
        "Disagree"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Strongly agree"
    }
  ]
}
